http://www.craftivf.com/privacy-statement

Privacy-Statement
This Privacy Notice was last updated on 22nd June 2018.
Craft provide insights into your pregnancy, your well-being and your baby's development, and provides you with personalised content, messages, tips and other services ("Services"). This Privacy Notice is meant to help you understand our privacy practices when you use our Services, including what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it, as well as your individual rights.
Craft uses personal data collected or processed by the Craft mobile application ("App").
This Privacy Notice applies to personal data collected or processed by the App, which is controlled by or under control of CRAFT Infertility Center or any of its affiliates or subsidiaries ("craft", "our", "we" or "us").
Please also read our Cookie Notice and Terms of Use, which describe the terms under which you use our Services.
What Personal Data are collected and for which Purposes.
We receive or collect personal data, as described in detail below, when we provide our Services, including when you access, download, install the Device or the App, or use our Services. We may use this personal data to perform the Services requested by you as a contractual necessity, to operate, provide, improve, customize, support and market our Services based on our legitimate interest, or to comply with a legal obligation to which we may be subject. If you do not want us to collect and process your personal data, you may not be able to use the Services.
Sensitive Personal Data
Before we collect sensitive personal data, we will inform you and ask your explicit consent. This data includes;
You may withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before withdrawing your consent.
Happenings @ Craft
06-12-2020A hospital with 100% non-donor IVF policy
29-11-2020A hospital with 100% non-donor IVF policy
READ ALL NEWS
Online Consultation
Welcome to 'ONLINE MEDICAL CONSULTATION' of CRAFT HOSPITAL AND RESEARCH CENTRE with our Specialist Doctor's
CRAFT panel of Doctors will provide you with an Online solution to your problem. Please note that we do not sell prescription drugs and do not provide you with a prescription. We can only give you advice and recommendation
Consult now
Home
About
Medical Services
Medical Team
Success Stories
Media Centre
Contact Us
© CRAFT Hospital & Research Centre. All rights reserved.
Designed and Developed by topservwebsoul.com
Need quick help?We can call you now or later.
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Iran (Islamic Republic of)
Slovakia (Slovak Republic)
Vatican City State (Holy See)
Venezuela
Viet Nam
Virgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
